[{"question": " oh, phoebe, are you still on hold? i was supposed to call my dad back like two hours ago.", "answer": " oh, yeah, he clipped on, he said call him as soon as you get a chance, he\u0092s at flimby\u0092s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " what\u0092s flimby\u0092s?", "answer": " oh, yeah, that\u0092s the word i use when i can\u0092t remember the real thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " okay. hang up! that\u0092s it! come on!", "answer": " no! rachel, that\u0092s what they want me to do. my warranty expires tomorrow, if i don\u0092t get through, they\u0092re not gonna fix my crappy, broken phone for free! we cannot let them win! it\u0092s us versus them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " ye-e-es!!", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " uh, listen i gotta double check for tickets tonight. who-who got what? chandler, phoebe, and rachel: i had one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " i need two. i\u0092m bringing pete. my boyfriend. i have a boyfriend now!", "answer": " two it is. ross, how about you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " uh, yeah, i ah, i also need two.", "answer": " really? who\u0092s number two?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " who\u0092s number two? one of the more difficult games sewer workers play.", "answer": " uh, no, it\u0092s-it\u0092s just this person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " like a date type  person?", "answer": " yeah, kinda. it\u0092s this woman from work. i hope that won\u0092t be too weird. will it, rach?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " no. no, not at all, not at all. i actually was gonna bring someone myself, so\u009a", "answer": " but you said one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " i meant, me plus one!", "answer": " okay.  did ah, you guys mean you plus one?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092ll see you tonight.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " okay, bye-bye!", "answer": " bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, hey, you guys are finally gonna get to meet kate!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  and i ah, borrowed some of your cologne. i hope she likes it.", "answer": " joey, what are you doing?! it\u0092s never gonna happen, she\u0092s seeing somebody.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " yeah, and i don\u0092t have any cologne.", "answer": " the green bottle next to the shaving cream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " thanks!", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " okay.  ooh, i\u0092m setting the phone down.  but i\u0092m still here! just don\u0092t go anywhere i\u0092m still here.  don\u0092t-don\u0092t switch or anything, \u0091cause i\u0092m, i\u0092m right here.  just one sec. one sec! one second!!  wait! one second! just\u009a", "answer": " phoebe?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " what?! monica, i\u0092m scared!!", "answer": " all right. honey, that\u0092s-that\u0092s a sleeve. okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " and! we also have speaker phone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " please, stay on the line. your call is important to us.", "answer": " okay, wait, you gotta hang up \u0091cause we\u0092re gonna be late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " thank you for your patience, you\u0092re the next caller.", "answer": " yes!! yes!! i\u0092m the next caller! you were gonna have me hang up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  hey! can you take a duck and a chick to the theatre?", "answer": " of course not.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " okay. i just wanted them to hear it from somebody else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " hey, hey rach!", "answer": " oh, hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " how are you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " good.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " so it\u0092s looks like we\u0092re the first ones here.", "answer": " yeah, looks that way. first ones here! wooo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh! tommy, this is ross. ross, tommy.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " okay, uhh, i think i\u0092m going to run to the ladies room.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " i\u0092ll join you.", "answer": " i\u0092ll get our seats.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " okay.   so uh, well, this-this is uh, this is awkward.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well y'know \u0091cause rachel and i used to go out.", "answer": " oh, i didn\u0092t, i didn\u0092t know that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh! well then this is awkward. so what do you uh\u009a", "answer": " i think we\u0092re here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh! yeah.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay.  uh, huh. excuse me, i\u0092m sorry, i-i think you may be in our seats.", "answer": " umm, no, i don\u0092t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " can-can we take a look at your ticket?", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  yep! yeah, see this says d-13, and uh\u009a", "answer": " oh, well i thought that ah\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " oh, you thought, huh? yeah, well that didn\u0092t really work out too well for you did it you idiot!! what are you?! a moron!! huh?! it says d-13! okay?! look you\u0092re surrounded by even numbers!! did that give you some clue?!", "answer": " uh, the usher told us to come\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " oh! oh! the usher must be right! what, with all that training they go through! get out!!  here!   hey man, you want the aisle?", "answer": " no, i\u0092m good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  there he is!", "answer": " there\u0092s our star!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " so, so, what\u0092d ya think?", "answer": " almost as good as that play with the two naked girls on the see-saw.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i-i wasn\u0092t in that.", "answer": " i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  oh-oh, hey-hey, kate! listen i want you to meet everybody. everybody, this is kate.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " so that\u0092s the girl you like.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": "  i\u0092m telling you, this guy rachel is with is crazy! okay? he viscously screamed at total strangers! i think he\u0092s baaad news!", "answer": " wait a minute, wait a minute, you don\u0092t like the guy rachel\u0092s dating? well, that\u0092s odd.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, hey, lauren. uh, you guys this is, this is kate\u0092s understudy, lauren.", "answer": " oh, hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey. gosh, you look soo familiar.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " so. how\u0092d you guys meet?", "answer": " well ah, the short version is, i ah pursued her for a couple of months, then i gave her a check for 20,000 dollars, and she was mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " joey, sweetheart, you were fabulous!", "answer": " hey you guys, this is my agent, estelle.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " how do you do.  ooh, you two girls were outstanding!  did they have representation?", "answer": " no, they-they weren\u0092t in the play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " we\u0092re not actors.", "answer": " ooh, what a shame! because with her face  and her chest  i could really put something together.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  hi! remember me?", "answer": " hi! yeah! tommy\u0092s in line for the bathroom and someone just cut in front of him, i think he\u0092s gonna snap.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " ross, i\u0092m gonna go.", "answer": " go? why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know. could be because i don\u0092t feel like standing around all night waiting for some guy who may or may not scream.", "answer": " but-but cailin, he definitely will scream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " good bye ross.", "answer": " uh, oh-ho bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": "  here we go people!  boxing day! the lucille lortel theatre, blah-la-la-la\u009a ah-ha! joey tribianni, gives an uneven performance, but mr. tribianni is not the worst thing in this production.", "answer": " yes!!! ha-ha-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " oh, is the play over?", "answer": " yeah. where were you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " thank you for your patience, you\u0092re the next caller.", "answer": " you were the next caller five hours ago. you must be going crazy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " hey! are you okay?", "answer": " fabulous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " listen, drama critics they\u0092re nothing but, but people who couldn\u0092t make it as actors. you know what you should do?", "answer": " become a drama critic!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " by the way, he dumped me tonight after he read my review.", "answer": " oh, classy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yep! i sure know how to pick \u0091em, huh? y'know i gave up a part on a soap for this!", "answer": " wow! yeah i ah, i gave up a job too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " really. what?", "answer": " uh, de-clawing cats. hey, tell ya what. let me walk you home. we\u0092ll stop by every news stand and burn every copy of their times and the post.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " why the post?", "answer": " oh, you didn\u0092t see the post?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " no. you?", "answer": " no. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  so you really think those newspapers are just jealous of me?", "answer": " oh, absolutely! you\u0092re talented and you\u0092re good looking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oh, you\u0092re sweet and cute.", "answer": " i know! that\u0092s why they trashed me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " whoa. wait a minute, wait a minute.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " i, i don\u0092t get you. i mean first, you hate me. then you sleep with me. then you want nothing to do with me, now you want me again.", "answer": " what? so you never went out with an actress before?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " kate, do you even like me?", "answer": " of course i do.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " well so, how come you blew me off? y'know? how come you were with him?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know! i just, just do this! i-i always have to pick the like the smartest guy, or-or the most talented guy\u009a why can\u0092t i just pick someone like you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " thanks.", "answer": " you know what i mean. i mean like the sweetest guy. joey, you\u0092re just so, you\u0092re so, so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " please stay on the line. you\u0092re call is very important to us.", "answer": "  pheebs, you\u0092ve been up for 24 hours! go to sleep, honey. th-this isn\u0092t healthy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no, no, i\u0092m fine, and y\u0092know why? \u0091cause of all the riboflavin.", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hey! didn\u0092t you have that outfit on last night?", "answer": " yeah! i stayed at kate\u0092s, but ah, nothing happened. hey, pheebs, where were ya?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i\u0092m so, so, so sorry, joey. i definitely am gonna see you\u0092re play. i swear you\u0092re play is very important to us, thank you for your patience. you\u0092re play is the next play is the next play i\u0092m gonna see.", "answer": " anyway, how did it go with kate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh, it was great! yeah, i-i walked her home, and it was amazing how much we connected, y'know? then ah, then she passed out, but then she woke up. yeah? and we stayed up all night talking, and now we\u0092re like totally crazy about each other!", "answer": " joey, you had the night!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " when two people finally realise their feelings for each other, and-and they talk for hours, and they-they learn all about the other person!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " you-you think?", "answer": " did you like learn about her family?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " two brothers, one died!", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " yeah?!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  this is from the woman at the bar.", "answer": " oh-ho-ho-ho.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " sorry. she thought you were somebody else.", "answer": " what time is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " one.", "answer": " one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " 7:15.  watch doesn\u0092t work.", "answer": " tommy\u0092s supposed to be here soon, we\u0092re going to lunch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " look. look, i wasn\u0092t going to say anything to you, but... all right, i don\u0092t think you should be seeing tommy anymore.", "answer": " you don\u0092t?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " no! the guy is mean. i mean really mean. i think you should stay away from him.", "answer": " umm, or, maybe, i should stay away from all men.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " no, it\u0092s not just \u0091cause i\u0092m jealous.  i mean i\u0092m not, i\u0092m not, i\u0092m not jealous, okay? it\u0092s\u009a look, the guy, he screamed, he actually screamed at this couple sitting in our seats.", "answer": " yeah, and at the end of the play, he, he got up y'know, and he just started like,  banging his hands together!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " we\u0092re kidding!", "answer": " ross, don\u0092t. ross! monica; ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " whoa!!", "answer": " whoa, sorry tommy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " what\u0092s in the cup, ross?", "answer": " umm\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " what is in the cup?!", "answer": " okay, it\u0092s coffee.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " ice coffee? tell me it\u0092s ice coffee!", "answer": " it\u0092s-it\u0092s hot\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": "  what\u0092s your favourite thing about summertime?", "answer": " umm, going to the beach. when it stays light real late.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah\u009a", "answer": "   hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " tommyyyy! say, what\u0092s your favourite thing about summer?", "answer": " ooh, i don\u0092t know. probably the smell of freshly cut grass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " sorry! sorry, i\u0092m late; sorry, i\u0092m late! my duck and my chick and a fight, it-it was ugly.", "answer": " look, we held the curtain for you buddy. come on, let\u0092s go! let\u0092s go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  vic! where have you been, baby?!", "answer": "    where\u0092s kate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": "  she got a job in l.a.", "answer": "  what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " i\u0092ve been waiting up all night for ya. where have you been?  where have you been? vic?!", "answer": " oh, ahh, go to the window. i\u0092m wanna run down to the truck and show you something.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": "  what do you got down there, vic? what do you got under that tarp?", "answer": "   when is she leaving?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  tonight. what are you doing?", "answer": "  i\u0092m coming up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " hey, mind if i use the phone?", "answer": " oh, i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " why don\u0092t you use ours across the hall, \u0091cause she\u009ahas\u009aproblems.", "answer": "  oh-ho, whoa! sorry, tommy. i almost spilled this hot coffee on you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah, but you didn\u0092t.", "answer": " no, but it\u0092s-it\u0092s-it\u0092s hot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " ross, would you just stop it! it\u0092s getting really old.", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe no one believes me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " i do, i believe you.", "answer": " you do pheebs?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " step away from the duck.", "answer": " ooh, sorry little mr. chic-a-dee, sorry you went doody in my hand!   well, i guess we\u0092re not going out anymore. whaa!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " joey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " i\u0092m soo glad i caught you, i couldn\u0092t find you before.", "answer": " wh-wh-what\u0092s going on? wh-what\u0092s this about l.a.?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " they still want me for general hospital.", "answer": " but, but wh-what about us?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " last night was wonderful. but i-i can\u0092t stay here just for you.", "answer": " well, so, stay for the museums!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " joey, onstage!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " well can you at least stay to the end of the play? i mean, i\u0092ll go to the airport with ya, i-i wanna say good bye.", "answer": "  where are you vic?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " flight\u0092s in an hour. i-i gotta go.", "answer": " vic! vic! vic!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " so this is it? victor?", "answer": " yeah, i guess it is.  listen, i ah, i gotta say good bye, and-and i gotta say it quick \u0091cause this is killing me. one thing you gotta know, is that i will never forget you. but, you\u0092ve got things you have to do now, and so do i. and so\u009a i\u0092m gonna get on this spaceship,  and i\u0092m gonna go to blargon 7 in search of alternative fuels. but when i return, 200 years from now, you\u0092ll be long gone. but i won\u0092t have aged at all.  so you tell your great-great-granddaughter to look me up, because adrienne, baby, i\u0092m gonna want to meet her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " phoebe, it\u0092s been two days.", "answer": " yeah, i know. oh, good thing it\u0092s one of those 801 numbers. right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " phoebe, 800 is toll free, 801 is-is utah.", "answer": " no, no, no, oh no-no-no, it\u0092s has to be 800.  \u0091cause all those big companies have 800 numbers, every one.  yeah, every big utah-based company has one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " phoe-be!!", "answer": " sorry, i\u0092m so sorry, i will pay you back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " and yet, she\u0092s still not hanging up the phone.", "answer": " hang it up! hang up the phone!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " fine! fine!  oh-oh!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " well, i think i broke it. but that\u0092s all right, here\u0092s the number you can call.", "answer": "  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep22.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}]